https://sttimothylutheran.com/privacy/

Google
Instagram Request PrayerOnline WorshipContact UsLearning Is Fun Preschool
Privacy NoticeLast updated: December 4, 2018This notice falls under the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).Who we areSt. Timothy Lutheran Church, ELCAOur website address is: https://www.sttimothylutheran.comSt. Timothy Lutheran Church is part of the ELCA. St. Timothy Lutheran is licensed by the federal government as a not-for-profit.Our Address: St. Timothy Lutheran Church1313 North Mill StreetNaperville, IL 60563St. Timothy Lutheran Church (STLC) operates the St. Timothy website, which provides business information for STLC. The website also provides the ability for users to sign up for an email subscription SERVICE.This page is used to inform website visitors regarding our policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decides to subscribe to STLC, or contact STLC through the Website at https://www.sttimothylutheran.comIf you choose to use our Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation with this policy. The Personal Information that we collect are used for providing and improving the website and STLC. We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.Information Collection and UseSTLC EMAIL SUBSCRIPTIONIf you have subscribed to the STLC email list SERVICE we collect the following data.Email address;First and Last Names;IP;  (this is an embedded part of the MailPoet email marketing plugin service utilized by this site – see details below.)EMAIL SUBSCRIPTION PROFILE DECISIONIf you sign up for our email list and STLC determines your subscription request is related to spam, malware, or other harmful intent to the STLC site, STLC reserves the right to decline or unsubscribe your subscription.  STLC email list is intended for subscribers who are friends of STLC or members of STLC who want to receive emails and notifications of STLC related news.COMMENTSWe do not allow comments on any posts or pages of our website at this time.Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service. (Comments are not allowed on any posts or pages at this time.)MEDIAIf you are an authorized editor of our website and upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.COOKIESCookies are files with small amount of data that is commonly used an anonymous unique identifier. These are sent to your browser from the website that you visit and are stored on your computer’s hard drive.We do not employ the use of cookies on our site.  However, the browser you use to view our site might.  Typically, these are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave comments and cookies usually will last for one year.If you are an authorized user of this site and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser. When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.EMBEDDED CONTENT FROM OTHER WEBSITESArticles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.Service ProvidersWe may employ third-party companies and individuals due to the following reasons:To facilitate our Service;To provide the Service on our behalf;To perform Service-related services; orTo assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.We want to inform our Service users that these third parties have access to your Personal Information. The reason is to perform the tasks assigned to them on our behalf. However, they are obligated not to disclose or use the information for any other purpose.If you are a subscriber to our email list service then your subscription data (first name, last name and email) is used by our email marketing plugin called MailPoet to analyze our email/marketing campaign success rates and in order to enable subscribers to manage their own subscription data. For further explanation on how your subscriber data is used by Mailpoet, please see their privacy statement. Services and Third Parties Where STLC Stores STLC DataSTLC relies on third party services to maintain its web site. STLC never shares or resells any of its data.Google Analytics (US).Google DriveGoogle PhotosGoogle directoryBing AnalyticsYouTube Channel (private)YOAST SEO plugin  Consent to CollectWe collect data from authorized users of the web site dashboard.The legal basis for us to collect the data is to be able to provide you with access to the website. SecurityWe value your trust in providing us your Personal Information, thus we are striving to use commercially acceptable means of protecting it. Please remember that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and reliable, and we cannot guarantee its absolute security.Links to Other SitesOur site may contain links to other sites. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that site. Note that these external sites are not operated by us. Therefore, we strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of these websites. We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party sites or services.Children’s PrivacyOur Services do not address anyone under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personal identifiable information from children under 13. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with personal information, please contact us so that we will be able to do necessary actions.Changes to This Privacy PolicyWe may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, we advise you to review this page periodically for any changes. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. These changes are effective immediately, after they are posted on this page.Print St. Timothy Lutheran Church of Naperville, IL Privacy Statement. Contact UsIf you have any questions or suggestions about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us.  You may contact St. Timothy Lutheran Church by filling out a contact form at https://sttimothylutheran.com/contact-us/
